bea.com 2000-08-15

# BEA Systems: Privacy Statement

### BEA Privacy Statement

BEA respects your right to privacy and your right to limit information exchanges to only those you initiate, if you so desire. We do acquire certain personal information from private individuals in the course of business, but we do not voluntarily share this personal information with third parties. We do use this information to better serve you and facilitate your use of our web site.

BEA may acquire a private individual's personal information from registration forms, product order information, or E-mail messages to us. Only those BEA employees who require this information to do their jobs will have access to it. The BEA web server also records visitor IP addresses and domain names for reporting and site usage analysis. This information is reported internally and then purged when required.

BEA will not voluntarily disclose a private individual's personal information to any third parties for marketing or promotional purposes, or for any other purpose unless a court orders us to. If, despite our security precautions, personal information about a private individual is inadvertently disclosed, we will do everything reasonable to limit and remedy the disclosure. However, BEA accepts no liability for any unintentional disclosure.

If you supply BEA with your E-mail address, postal address or phone number through our site you may receive promotional or informational communications from BEA. If you prefer not to receive these communications or if you have any questions about how we use the information you provide, please send an E-mail message to us at [webmaster@beasys.com](mailto:webmaster@beasys.com). 

| 
### BEA Privacy Statement

BEA respects your right to privacy and your right to limit information exchanges to only those you initiate, if you so desire. We do acquire certain personal information from private individuals in the course of business, but we do not voluntarily share this personal information with third parties. We do use this information to better serve you and facilitate your use of our web site.

BEA may acquire a private individual's personal information from registration forms, product order information, or E-mail messages to us. Only those BEA employees who require this information to do their jobs will have access to it. The BEA web server also records visitor IP addresses and domain names for reporting and site usage analysis. This information is reported internally and then purged when required.

BEA will not voluntarily disclose a private individual's personal information to any third parties for marketing or promotional purposes, or for any other purpose unless a court orders us to. If, despite our security precautions, personal information about a private individual is inadvertently disclosed, we will do everything reasonable to limit and remedy the disclosure. However, BEA accepts no liability for any unintentional disclosure.

If you supply BEA with your E-mail address, postal address or phone number through our site you may receive promotional or informational communications from BEA. If you prefer not to receive these communications or if you have any questions about how we use the information you provide, please send an E-mail message to us at [webmaster@beasys.com](mailto:webmaster@beasys.com). 

|
